https://www.armarkat.com/privacy-policy

Created with Sketch.
Created with Sketch.
All Classic Cat Trees
Extra Small Cat Trees (under 30")
Small Cat Trees (31" to 45")
Medium Cat Trees (46" to 69")
Large Cat Trees (70" to 76")
Extra Large Cat Trees (over 76")
All Premium Cat Trees
small under 45"
medium 46" to 69"
large 70" to 76"
extra large over 76"
Privacy Policy
Armarkat.com is committed to protecting your privacy. The information we collect is used only used to process orders and to provide support to you.
What information do we collect? How do we use it?
When you order, we request your name, email address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date. This allows us to process, track and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order’s status.
How do we protect customer information?
We use a secure server for collecting personal and credit card information. The secure server layer (SSL) encrypts (scrambles) all of the information you enter before it is transmitted over the internet to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.
What about "cookies"?
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We do not use cookies to collect or store any information about visitors or customers.
Will we disclose the information collected to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We may release account information only when we believe, in good faith, that such release is necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of ourselves, our users, or others.
Your Consent
By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by armarkat.com. If at any time we change this privacy policy, we will post such changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it.
Please note: When posting comments on this website, you give implicit consent that they may be used for promotional purposes by armarkat.com
In Summary
Armarkat.com is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make shopping at armarkat.com as simple as possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.
Questions and Feedback
If you have any questions or feedback related to this Privacy Policy, please email us at webmaster@armarkat.com
Have a Happy Thanksgiving to our Cats!
How to Choose the Right Cat Tree for Both Yourself and Your Feline…
